- How cool?
- Yes, that was tough.
That you continued to swim around even though you just got bitten by a turtle.
Yes, what can one say?
It was fun.
Alma was thus four years on this trip, you would be five.
Harry was two and a half.
- Now we are going to jump to the country place, where we are now.
- Yes, our first summer on Youtube.
(Here's our pool, with a lot of scrap in.)
- Our pool!
- Where is the water?
Alma, your style!
- Check out my glasses, they are round.
- Yes.
(- Listen, what kind of sunglasses are you wearing?) (- They're no sunglasses.)
(- What is it, then?) (- only glasses.)
It is so terrible.
That we could live here!
It was a nightmare, that is.
- Yes.
But it's pretty good peep.
- Because it's pretty nice here now.
- Yes.
Now we arrive at the first trip to Kolmården.
(- Didn't you dare to cuddle with the wolf?) (- No-ä, I want to cuddle with you!)
(Yes ... I love to cuddle with you.)
(- I want to cuddle with him.) (- Do you want it now?)
(- Yes-a.) (- Do it, then. He stands there because he wants to hug you.)
(He was very nice!)
(What good that you dared.)
- Oh, Harry.
- "Cuddly".
(LESSPAR)
"He was very nice!".
(Will they cut into my tongue?)
(No, that's what they should not do. They have a tool that holds the tongue.)
(The knife cuts and then they burn the wound surface as well, so it doesn't bleed.)
(What will I dream about? I want to dream that I go skateboard every day.)
(We must not film. See you after the operation.)
(VINKI-VINK.)
Gull kid!
And I was sooo nervous.
- Look, you look like you've seen a ghost.
- mm.
(- You look like you've seen a ghost.) (- Yes but I'm really rally.)
- Nämen ... I can't remember.
- Neither do I.
- huh?!
- Yes!
This is from the program "Wanted" in 2006. How many years ago is it?
- What will it be ... 13 years ago.
- Yes.
Excuse the quality and how compressed the picture was, but then it was at that time.
Mom Joanna is in London anyway and reports on Jack the Ripper.
(The mystery surrounding Jack The Ripper has been raising people for over a century.)
(He murdered and cut up at least five women in London's East End.)
(Axel) Nämen God.
(... and even today no one can say for sure who Jack the Ripper really was.)
Nämen look, there goes mom!
It was a huge card, but I wanted to bid on it.
Imagine what you can find in Youtube's treasure chamber!